export const questions = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "What is the capital city of Kenya?",
      options: ["Kampala", "Nairobi", "Runda", "Rwanda"],
      answer: "Nairobi"
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "What is the most popular food in Kenya?",
      options: ["Githeri", "Chapati", "Taco", "Pizza"],
      answer: "Chapati"
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "When did Kenya attain independence?",
      options: [1963, 1964, 1965, 1966],
      answer: 1963
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "Which County in Kenya is an island?",
      options: ["Nairobi", "Mombasa", "Kisumu", "Lamu"],
      answer: "Mombasa"
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "Which generation comes before Gen Z?",
      options: ["B.Boomers", "Gen X", "Millennials", "Gen Z"],
      answer: "Millennials"
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "At what age does one apply for a national ID?",
      options: [18, 19, 20, 34],
      answer: 18
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "Who is not an African artist?",
      options: ["Kendrick", "Burna Boy", "Wizkid", "Davido"],
      answer: "Kendrick"
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "Who is not an American rapper?",
      options: ["Central C", "Kendrick", "Drake", "Travis"],
      answer: "Central C"
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "Which one is not an airport?",
      options: ["Kisumu", "Nairobi", "Moi", "JKIA"],
      answer: "Nairobi"
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "Which is not a city?",
      options: ["Kampala", "Kiambu", "Nairobi", "Kisumu"],
      answer: "Kiambu"
    }
  ];